<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>OakTown 4-H</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on OakTown 4-H</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 13:07:31 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Why join OakTown 4-H?</title>
      <link>/whyjoin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Oct 2018 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/whyjoin/</guid>
      <description>The goal of 4-H is to develop citizenship, leadership, responsibility and life skills in youth through experiential learning programs and a positive youth development approach. We strive to engage youth to reach their full potential, working and learning with caring adults. The 4-H motto is “To make the best better”, while its slogan is “Learn by doing”. A recent report from Tufts University shows that 4-H youth excel beyond their peers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About 4-H</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>The 4-H Youth Development Program is in every county in California. 4-H is a an organization where young people, 5–19, are given opportunities to build confidence, learn responsibility, and develop skills that will last them a lifetime. It’s an organization where youth make friends and share interests, ranging from building robots to raising rabbits, designing web pages to landscape design. 4-H is where youth work together to make a positive difference in their community, and adult volunteers make a powerful difference in the lives of young people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>You may contact me through the nearest wormhole This is where my great contact goes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Have a 4-H Record Book?</title>
      <link>/record-books/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 15:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/record-books/</guid>
      <description>The 4-H program has a long history of record keeping. This focus reflects the importance of this life skill in our daily lives. In 4-H, young people track their activities, events, profits and losses, skill development and learning experiences.Completing a 4-H Record Book is a process where 4-H members record project and club work.
4-H Record Books serve a variety of purposes:
 4-H Record Books encourage members to set goals, pursue strategies to meet those goals, and to shift gears in the face of challenges and obstacles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 13:07:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archives</title>
      <link>/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jul 2015 13:50:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Club Calendar</title>
      <link>/calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/calendar/</guid>
      <description>Calendar</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
